Fear takes flight.
Red Eye is a thriller, mystery film directed by Wes Craven.
An overnight flight to Miami quickly becomes a battle for survival when Lisa realizes her seatmate plans to use
her as part of a chilling assassination plot against the Deputy Secretary of Homeland Security.
If she refuses to cooperate, her own father will be killed.
As the miles tick by, she's in a race against time to find a way to
warn the potential victims before it's too late.
Lisa Reisert, played by Rachel McAdams.
Jackson Rippner, played by Cillian Murphy.
Joe Reisert, played by Brian Cox.
Cynthia, played by Jayma Mays.
Dep. Sec. Charles Keefe, played by Jack Scalia.
Bob Taylor, played by Robert Pine.
Red Eye is a 2005 American psychological thriller film directed by Wes Craven and
written by Carl Ellsworth, based on a story by Ellsworth and Dan Foos.
It stars Rachel McAdams, Cillian Murphy, and Brian Cox.
The story follows a hotel manager ensnared in an assassination plot by
a terrorist while aboard a red-eye flight to Miami.
The film score was composed and conducted by Marco Beltrami.
It was distributed by DreamWorks Pictures and released on August 19, 2005.
The film received positive reviews.
An extended version of the film, which added previously unused footage to increase the
running time, was broadcast on the ABC television network several times.
The film explores themes of hotel, airplane, airport, miami, florida, hitman.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.